<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<welcomePage 
	title="Welcome to the Project Development Tools">

	<intro>This Feature will be support  a set of tools for development of database applications. In a first step this feature 
	should support helpers for develop applications with JDO access.
	</intro>
	
	<item><b>Update the Feature</b> Please open the update perspective and add a new update site for this plugin.
	The URL for the update site is: http://devtool.sourceforge.net</item>
	<item><b>Preference Page</b> This Plugin contribute a peference page named "JDO". Here you can add the 
	libraries of your jdo provider. The most jdo provider distribute a set of jar files wich must be added to the project 
	classpath. These files you can put in a list at the JDO preference page.</item>
	
	<item><b>JDO Nature</b> If you have a project wich is a application with JDO access, so you can go to the 
	java perspective and click on the right mouse button. The context menu JDO will be occure. Now you can add
	or remove the JDO Nature to or from the choose project(s). If you add the JDO nature to a project, the jar files 
	from the JDO prefenrence page will be added to the project classpath. If you remove the JDO Nature so only the
	classpath entries wich begins with JDO_  will be removed from the project classpath.</item>
	
	<item><b>JDO Descriptor Wizzard</b> If you click on a geen class icon, such as outline of class, then in the JDO
	context menu you can build a JDO descriptor for the choosen class.</item>
	
	<item><b>JDO Enhancement</b>The JSR 12 of Sun (JDO Specification) support 2 methods for a
	class to implements the JDO contracts. First the class can explizit implements the PersistenceCapable interface or
	the byte code of class will be enhanced by a enhancer. 
	The author of this plugin  think: It is a good idea to implements explizit the interface PersistenceCapable and only 
	enhance the byte code of third party classes. So this plugin support for classes in the JDO context menu a item 
	to implements the interface PersistenceCapable.</item>
	
</welcomePage>





